Matt Homan

1102 Speight Avenue •

Waco, TX 76798

www.linkedin.com/in/matt-homan

(972) 467-7789 · Matt_Homan1@baylor.edu

CAREER PROFILE

Cybersecurity-based MIS student who excels at communication and problem solving. Committed worker with an abundance of experience in thinking outside-the-box. Strong leader that is able to deliver results on time. Technologically skilled and able to pick up on new skills quickly and efficiently. A wealth of experience in fast-paced, high-pressure environments.

EDUCATION

Baylor University - Waco, Texas

May 2024

Bachelor of Business Administration

- Major: Management Information Systems
- Dean's Academic Honor List: Fall 2022

EXPERIENCE

Baylor University - Waco, Texas

Nov 2023 - Present

Cybersecurity Research Assistant

- Overseeing facility and systems at Central Texas Cyber Range in Baylor Research Innovation Collaborative
- · Managing VMWare vSphere server used by students and faculty to simulate cybersecurity environments

Researching application of core cybersecurity concepts into Industrial Control Systems

Baylor University - Waco, Texas

Aug 2022 - Nov 2023

Cybersecurity Research Assistant

- Managing a private cloud testing environment that is used for virtualization of real-world cybersecurity applications and systems
- Developing strategy and technology for automation for virtualized hardware and software deployment on a VMWare vSphere server cluster using Ansible and Terraform
- Researching application of core cybersecurity concepts into Industrial Control Systems

Royse City ISD - Royse City, Texas

May 2022 - Aug 2022

Technology Specialist Intern

- Engineered python script that automated address locating for school district, saving several days' worth of work
- Created efficient inventory system for parts and devices
- Assisted teachers and administrators in quickly diagnosing and fixing their various computer hardware and software issues

ADDITIONAL

 Computer Skills: VMWare vSphere, Linux, Windows Server/Active Directory, ProxMox, C++, Java, MySQL, Apache2, nginx

•	Organizations: Captain of the Baylor Collegiate Cyber Defense Competition team, Founder and	

President of Baylor Cybersecurity Club, Computing for Compassion member

• Awards: WACODE 2022 Hackathon Novice bracket winner